<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
<publisher>Public Health</publisher>
<publisherurl>http://publichealthcareers.org</publisherurl>
<job>
<title><![CDATA[Accountant]]></title>
<date><![CDATA[2022-11-30]]></date>
<referencenumber><![CDATA[17840788]]></referencenumber>
<url><![CDATA[http://publichealthcareers.org/job/accountant-us-xx-springfield-17849999-999/99></url>
<company><![CDATA[XX Department of Public Health (GDPH)]]></company>
<city><![CDATA[Springfield]]></city>
<state><![CDATA[XX]]></state>
<country><![CDATA[US]]></country>
<description><![CDATA[<div><p><strong>Connect passion with purpose.</strong> The XX Department of Public Health is the lead agency entrusted by the people of XX to proudly protect lives and promote healthy lifestyles in diverse communities statewide. We are committed to the health of the population of XX as our work impacts past, present and future generations.<br>  <br><strong>What we offer.</strong> Enjoy a generous benefits package that includes a flexible work schedule, unique training opportunities, engaging worksite wellness events, wellness breaks, lactation rooms, <u>employee retirement plan</u>, <u>deferred compensation</u>, <u>13 paid holidays</u>, <u>vacation and sick leave</u>, <u>dental</u>, <u>vision</u>, <u>long term care</u>, and <u>life insurance</u>; in addition to telework opportunities depending on the position.<br>  <br><strong>Make your mark in public service.</strong> As an accredited public health department, we're seeking a highly qualified candidate for the position of <strong><em>Accountant</em></strong><strong> </strong>within the Division of Brain &amp; Spinal Trust Fund Commission located in Springfield, GA.<br> <br>Won't you join us?</p> <p><strong>Job Responsibilities:</strong></p> <p>Under general supervision, analyzes financial information and prepares financial reports to document or maintain records of assets, liabilities, profit and loss or other financial activities within an agency. Evaluates, audits and maintains accounts and transaction processing to ensure GAAP compliance. Reports to the Executive Director.<br><br>Note: This is a “Hybrid” position which may allow a flexible working environment in-office and remote.</p> <p><strong>Minimum Qualifications:</strong></p> <p>Completion of a bachelor's degree in accounting from an accredited college or university <strong>AND</strong> One year of professional accounting experience,<br><br><strong>OR </strong><br><br>Completion of a bachelor's degree in a business curriculum which included completion of<br>introductory and intermediate accounting sequence <strong>AND</strong> One year of professional accounting experience,<br><br><strong>OR</strong><br><br>Completion of a master's degree in accounting.  <br><br><strong>Note:</strong> Some positions may require certifications.</p> <div><a><i></i> Create a Job Alert for Similar Jobs</a></div><div><div><div><div>About XX Department of Public Health (GDPH)</div><div><div>XX Department of Public Health Commissioner and leaders encourages all employees to engage in regular wellness activities and to make lifestyle choices that promote health and well-being.The use of wellness breaks during the workday is authorized to support this philosophy and assist employees in meeting their wellness goals.  A maximum of 30 minutes in a given workday may be used to engage in wellness activities, generally in the form of two 15-minute breaks or one 30-minute break.Employment InformationCurrent State employees are subject to State Personnel Board rules regarding salary.DPH accepts educational credential recognized by the Council for Higher Education Accreditation (CHEA) and/or the US Department of Education (DOE) will be considered. DPH will contact educational institutions to verify degree, diploma, licensure, etc.The candidate selected for this position may be subject to pre-employment drug screening and a criminal background check.As an employee of DPH, in the event of an identified emergency you may be required, as a term and condition of employment, to assist in meeting the emergency responsibilities of the department.If you re<span>...</span><span>quire accommodations under the American Disability Act (ADA), email request by the closing date of this announcement to: DPH-HR@dph.ga.gov.DPH is an Equal Opportunity EmployerDue to the volume of applications received, we are unable to provide information on application status by phone or e-mail. All qualified applicants will be considered, but may not necessarily receive an interview. Selected applicants will be contacted by the hiring agency for next steps in the selection process. Applicants who are not selected will not receive notification.This position is subject to close at any time once a satisfactory applicant pool has been identified.</span><div>Show more</div><div>Show less</div></div></div></div><a><i></i> <span>Connections working at XX Department of Public Health (GDPH)</span></a></div></div></div>]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Operations]]></category>
<jobtype><![CDATA[]]></employmenttype>
<salary><![CDATA[$60800.00 - $101400.00 per year]]></salary>
</job>
</source>
